Guide to the Catalogue Department, Yale University Library, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1924-2008; Accession 2015-A-053
  - Acquisitions: US-UK Vendor Review, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Proposals for US/UK Monographic Acquisitions, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Proposals for Monographic Approval/Plans, Firm Orders and Shelf-Relay Services, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Association of Research Libraries: Emetrics, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - US/UK Monographic Acquisitions, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - E-Team: Planning Documents, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Association of Research Libraries: Surveys, 2004-2006 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Association of Research Libraries: Government Documents, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Vender Review Task Force, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Workflow Memos 1, 1971-1985 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Workflow Memos 2, 1983-1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Cataloging Memos, 1976-2004 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Serials Division Adding Manual, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Process Improvements, 1984-2000 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Catalog Department Miscellaneous, 1952-1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Workflow Memos 3, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Yale Dissertations, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Frontlog Proposals, 1991-1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Reclassification and Recataloging, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cataloging/Humanities Memos, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Processing Service Team, 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Processing Services, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Social Science Library, 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Review Plaza, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Research Library Group Fixed Agreement, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Research Library Group Access, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Research Library Group Fiscal Year 2005 Contract, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Research Library Group - Elkington Visit, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Research Library Group - Annual Contract, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Research Library Group - General, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Research Library Group - Collaboration, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Research Library Group - Cultural Materials Initiatives, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Latin American Recon, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Collections Collaborative records, 2004-2008; Accession 2016-A-051
  Restricted until January 1, 2044.
  - General files, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Extensible catalog project, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Final report, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Getty Museum visit-notes and correspondence, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ITLS-draft task list, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Interim reports, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meetings-agendas and correspondence, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Meetings-agendas, invitations and correspondence, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mellon-grant fiscal proposal, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mellon proposal, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Metadata guidelines, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Other projects-PACSCL, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Program events, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Project web site, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Research Libraries Group (RLG), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Re-grants, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Re-grant projects-collection guides, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Re-grant projects-primary sources at Yale website, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Re-grant projects-World War I portal, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Special Collections-notes, case studies and ephemera, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Special Collections sub-committee correspondence, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Steering Committee mailing list, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Steering Committee-notes, agendas and minutes, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Surveys-drafts and notes, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Records, 1919-2014; 1990-2014; Accession 2016-A-077
  - Administrative files
    - MARC Holdings in NOTIS, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Serial Access Level Records: Final Report, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - SML Office Renovation, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Cross-Training Initiative, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Orbis Introduction, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Voyager 5.0 Checklist, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Online Public Access Catalog (OPAC), 2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Orientation for AACR2, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Monographs Cataloging, 1985-2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Subject Manual, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Voyager 2000 Manuals (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Orbis Cataloging, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Humanities Workflow, 1983-1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Processing Service Memos, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Predictive Pattern Policies, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Belletristic, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Religion Working Group, 1972-1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Art Metadata, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Film Studies Center Project, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Yale Care, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Technical Service Reorganization Plan, 1988-1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Minimal Level Cataloging, 1976-1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - RLA Beinecke, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Western Americana, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Monk MARC, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Retrospective Conversion - Contracts, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Walpole Collection, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Charpentier Report, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Classification Decisions Committee, 1949-1973 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Yale Library Correspondances, 1970-1983 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Research Library Group Cultural Materials Alliance, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - SSL/Mudd Library, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Social Science Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - SSL/Mudd Miscellaneous, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Social Science - Economic Growth, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - SSLIS: StatLab, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Preservation Department Survey - SSL, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - GPO Digitization, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Meetings on Digital Preservation, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - CIS Microfiche Library Catalog Records, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Inter-University Consortium for Political and Social Research, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Social Science - Digital Archiving, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Mudd Floor Plans, 2002-2007 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - SSLIS: Lowers Risk Evaluation Report, 9/2002006 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - SSL - StatLab, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Serials Summit: Pt.1, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Serials Summit: Pt.2, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Shelf Ready Final Report, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Shelf Ready Books, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Shelf Ready Book Proposal, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Serials Notes, 1947-1951 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Serials Catalog: Third Edition 1, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Serials Catalog: Third Edition 2, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Serials Catalog: Second Edition, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Machine-Aided Technical Processing System, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Sample Card Typing Manual 1, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Sample Card Typing Manual 2, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Call Numbers: Miscellaneous, 1984-1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Call Numbers: Yale Classifications, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Call Numbers: Label Printing Indexing, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Study Group Interim Report: Card Form Bib Records, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Public Card Catalog, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Filing Lessons, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Filing Code for Departmental Libraries, 1954-1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - NOTIS Programmer's Reference Manual, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - USMARC Specifications for Record Structure, Character Sets, Tapes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - RLIN MARC Record: Description and Interpretation, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Program LYS10000 (RLIN to NOTIS Conversion), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Orbis Cataloging: Keyword, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Orbis Cataloging: Maintenance, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Orbis Cataloging: Authority Control, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Purchase Agreement for an Automated Library Circulation System, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Orbis Cataloging: Introduction (First Copy), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Orbis Cataloging: Memo Series (First Copy), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Orbis Cataloging: Introduction (Second Copy), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Orbis Cataloging: Memo Series (Second Copy), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Library Policy Manual 1, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Library Policy Manual 2, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Online Shelflist, 1996-2001 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Process Improvement: Implementation Architecture, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Process Improvement: Miscellaneous, 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Serial Department Accession, 1935-1939 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Processing Service Memos 1, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Processing Service Memos 2, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Processing Service Memos 3, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Processing Service Memos 4, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Processing Service Memos 5, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Processing Service Memos 6, 1990-1996 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Processing Service Memos 7, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Processing Service Memos 8, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Retro Link Associates Proposal for Retrospective Conversion Section 1-6, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Retro Link Associates Proposal for Retrospective Conversion Section 7-9, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - COCI: Review Subgroup, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - COCI: Minutes + Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - COCI: Committee on Catalog Continuation, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - COCI: Request for Information, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - COCI: History, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Subject Manual 1, 1967-1978 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Subject Manual 2, 1967-1978 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Catalog Department Orientation Program, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Filing Manual, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - MATPS Processing: Background, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - MATPS Processing: Current, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - MATPS Processing: Conversion Specs, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - MATPS Processing: Original, 1978-1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Acquisition Project I Part 1, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Acquisition Project I Part 2, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Acquisition Project I Part 3, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Acquisition Project I Part 4, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Acquisition Project I Part 5, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - RLIN Location Tables for Use, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - RLIN MARC Record: Description and Interpretation, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Serial System Study 1, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Serial System Study 2, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Serials: Flextime, 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Serials: Printouts, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Serials: Departmental, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Serials: Adding PRR, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Serials: Typing No List, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Serials: General, 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Catalog Department Manual 1, 1954-1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Catalog Department Manual 2, 1954-1968 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Orbis Acquisition Manual 1, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Orbis Acquisition Manual 2, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Orbis Acquisition Manual 3, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Orbis Acquisition Manual 4, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - NOTIS User's Guide 1, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - NOTIS User's Guide 2, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - NOTIS User's Guide 3, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - NOTIS User's Guide 4, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - GEAC Conversion: Tests Production Runs, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - GEAC Conversion: Specifications, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - GEAC Conversion: Design, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - GEAC Conversion: Source Code, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Process Improvement: Steering Committee, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Catalog Cards Typing Manual, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Organization Committee on the Reorganization of the Catalogue Department, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Machine Aided Technical Processing System, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - RLIN Conversion Specifications 1, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - RLIN Conversion Specifications 2, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - RLIN Conversion Specifications 3, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - RLIN Conversion Misc, 1988-1995 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - RLIN Conversion Problems/Fixes, 1988-1997 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Organization of the Yale University Library (Cataloging Department), 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Yale Library Orientation, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - GEAC Misc, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - GEAC Tables, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - GEAC Data Dictionaries, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - GEAC Specs, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Data Migration: Voyager, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Data Migration: Holdings Items, Acquisition, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Data Migration: Data Cleanup, Group Change Meetings, Bibliographic, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Data Migration: Changes, Recalls/Holds, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Data Migration: Patron, Fines/Fees, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Data Migration: Auth, Vendor, Order, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Data Migration: Bibliographic, Holdings, Item, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Data Migration: Misc 1, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Data Migration: Misc 2, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Managerial and Professional Job Description 1, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Managerial and Professional Job Description 2, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Managerial and Professional Job Description 3, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Managerial and Professional Job Description 4, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Managerial and Professional Job Description 5, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Business Office: Updated Yale Travel Policies (First Copy), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Business Office: Updated Yale Travel Policies (Second Copy), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Office Procedures Manual, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Personnel Policies and Practices: Memos, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Personnel Policies and Practices: Appendix, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Personnel Policies and Practices: Performance and Conduct/Grievances, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Personnel Policies and Practices: Staff Development, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Personnel Policies and Practices: Workplace Practices, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Personnel Policies and Practices: Leaves of Absence, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Personnel Policies and Practices: Benefits, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Personnel Policies and Practices: Compensation and Classification, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Personnel Policies and Practices: Employment, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Personnel Policies and Practices: Introduction, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Facts: Yale University Library, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Triage Option for the Retrospective Conversion, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Rules for Marking (Copy 3), 1970s (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Serials Division Adding Manual, 1964-1988 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - MARC Format Review Project, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Serials Catalog: Third Edition 1 (second copy), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Serials Catalog: Third Edition 2 (second copy), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Serials System Study 1 (first copy), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Serials System Study 2 (first copy), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Serials System Study 3 (first copy), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Serials System Study 4 (first copy), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Serials System Study 1 (second copy), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Serials System Study 2 (second copy), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Serials System Study 3 (second copy), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Serials System Study 4 (second copy), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - The Esstential Yale in 6,500,000 volumes, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Catalog Department Manual 1 (first copy), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Catalog Department Manual 2 (first copy), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Catalog Department Manual 1 (second copy), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Catalog Department Manual 2 (second copy), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Filing Lessons: Official and Public Catalogues, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Subject Manual, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - OCLC/WLN MARS Authority Control, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - ORBIS General Introduction, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Glossary of Library Terms, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - The Card Catalog, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Selective Book Retirement Program: Manual of Procedures, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - An Introduction to ORBIS in Staff Mode, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Sample Card Manual (First Copy), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Sample Card Manual (Second Copy), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - NJ 18 Call number System, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Catalogue Department Manual 1, 1949-1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Catalogue Department Manual 2, 1949-1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Catalogue Department Manual 3, 1949-1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Catalogue Department Manual 4, 1949-1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Catalogue Department Manual Draft 1, 1949-1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Catalogue Department Manual Draft 2, 1949-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Catalogue Department Manual Draft 3, 1949-1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Catalogue Department Manual Draft 4, 1949-1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Catalogue Department Manual Draft 5, 1949-1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Auction Catalogs, 1981-1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Auction and Sales Catalogues Manual (First Copy), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Auction and Sales Catalogues Manual (Second Copy), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - SCIPIO - Art Sales Catalog Database, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Sales and Auction Catalogs, 1986-1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Proposal for Automated Authority Control Services for Yale University, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Proposal for Retrospective Conversion Services for Yale University, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Subject Classification for the British History OCLC Retrospective Conversion Project, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - British History OCLC Retrospective Conversion Memos, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Examples of OCLC Catalog for British History Load, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Specifications for British History OCLC Load, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Retrospective Conversion Agreement Between Yale University Library and OCLC, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Serials Catalog: Third Edition 1 (Third Copy), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Serials Catalog: Third Edition 2 (Third Copy), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Catalog Department Manual 1 (Third Copy), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Catalog Department Manual 2 (Third Copy), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Subject Manual (Second Copy), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Response to Yale University Library Retrospective Conversion Request for Proposal, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Orbis Cataloging: Introduction (Third Copy), 1989 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Orbis Cataloging: Memo Series (Third Copy), 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - OCLC Conversion, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - RLA Conversion 1, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - RLA Conversion 2, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - RLA Conversion 3, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Gale MARC Record Purchase Agreement, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - DLF: Steering Committee Meeting 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - DLF: Steering Committee Meeting 2003 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - DLF: Fall Forum 2003 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - DLF: Distributed Open Digital Library Event, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - DLF: Aquifer Letter of Intent, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - DLF: Aquifer User Studies, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - DLF: Steering Committee, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - DSDM: Project Management Training Documents, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - E-Resources Management Task Force, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - E-Resources Mangement Activities Workshop, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - E-Collections: Electronic Resources Workflow LifeCycle, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - E-Resources: Technical Services, 2009-2010 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Electronic Collections, 2008-2010 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Egyptology/AOS, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Digital Landscapes: Cyberinfrastructure Survey Data, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Digital Inventory, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Casalini I, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Casalini II, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Center for Science Social Science Information (CSSSI), 2010 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Catalog - Open House Fliers and Maps, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Technical Services Reorganization Task Force, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Catalog and Metadata Services Strategic Plan I, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Catalog and Metadata Services Strategic Plan II, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Catalog and Metadata Services Strategic Plan III, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Catalog and Metadata Services Strategic Plan, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Cooperative Catalog I, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Cooperative Catalog II, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - FY15 Budget, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Archivists Toolkit, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Assistant Manual, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Assistant Manual, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - ARL: Special Collections, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - American Oriental Society (AOS), 1956-2012 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - ARTstor Shared Shelf Complex Objects, 2009-2011 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - ARTstor Shared Shelf I, 2007-2009 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - ARTstor Shared Shelf II, 2007-2009 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - ARTstor: Example, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - ARTstor Hosting Agreement, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Arts Library: Arts Library, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Acquisitions: Operations Plan, 2004-2008 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Acquisitions: Annual Report 2006 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Acquisitions: Annual Report 2010 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Acquisitions: Reorganization Documents, 1987-1991 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Acquisitions: Ordering Flowcharts, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Catalog Department Strategic Vision, 2007-2011 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Authority Control Contract, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Babylonian Collection: Progress Report to Mellon Foundation, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 40)